<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.faktorips.feature.nls1"
      label="Faktor-IPS German Language Pack"
      version="3.11.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="Faktor Zehn AG"
      license-feature="org.faktorips.license">

   <description url="http://www.faktorips.org">
      Faktor-IPS - German Language Pack
Dieses Paket enthält die deutschen Übersetzungen für Faktor-IPS. Um auch die von Eclipse mitgebrachten Funktionen auf deutsch zu sehen, müssen Sie zusätzlich das deutsche Sprachpacket von Eclipse.org installieren.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.faktorzehn.org">
      Copyright (c) Faktor Zehn AG. &lt;http://www.faktorzehn.org&gt;

This source code is available under the terms of the AGPL Affero General Public License version 3 and if and when this source code belongs to the faktorips-runtime or faktorips-valuetype component under the terms of the LGPL Lesser General Public License version 3. 

Please see LICENSE.txt for full license terms, including the additional permissions and the possibility of alternative license terms.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.faktorzehn.org">
      Faktor IPS is available under a dual licensing scheme whereby use of Faktor IPS in projects that are licensed 
so as to be compatible with AGPL Version 3 – or in respect of a faktorips-runtime or faktorips-valuetype 
component with LGPL version 3 - may use Faktor IPS under the terms of the compatible license. Please see 
agpl-3.0.txt and lgpl-3.0.txt in the Faktor IPS package for more details. However, if this licensing is 
incompatible with your use of Faktor IPS, alternative license terms are available from Faktor Zehn AG.                    

In case you use Faktor IPS under the aforementioned terms, the following additional permission are stated: If 
you modify the Program (in respect to the defintion of the AGPL or LGPL), or any covered work, by linking or 
combining it with libraries of the namespace org.eclipse.* and org.junit (including dependencies or a modified 
version of these libraries), containing parts covered by the terms of Eclipse Public License Version 1.0 (EPL), 
the licensors of this Program grant you additional permission to convey the resulting work.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.faktorips.devtools.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.faktorips.devtools.core.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.faktorips.devtools.tableconversion"/>
      <import plugin="org.faktorips.devtools.htmlexport"/>
      <import plugin="org.faktorips.devtools.stdbuilder"/>
      <import plugin="org.faktorips.devtools.stdbuilder.ui"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.faktorips.nls.devtools.core.nl1"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.faktorips.nls.devtools.core.ui.nl1"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.faktorips.devtools.tableconversion.nl1"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.faktorips.devtools.htmlexport.nl1"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.faktorips.nls.devtools.stdbuilder.nl1"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.faktorips.nls.devtools.stdbuilder.ui.nl1"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
